





Melbourne



linkedin.com/in/hsinclair23/



github.com/Hughsin23



**EDUCATION** 

Software Engineering (Immersive)
GENERAL ASSEMBLY
2021-2022

Bachelor of Arts - International Studies **RMIT UNIVERSITY** 

#### 2016-2020

- RMIT mentoring program
- RMIT cultural exchange program

Diploma of Languages (Japanese Intensive) **RMIT UNIVERSITY** 

## 2015-2015

- RMIT mentoring program
- RMIT cultural exchange program



**SKILLS** 

Javascript | VS Code | React | HTML | CSS Ruby | Sinatra | GitHub | Node | Rails | Bilingual (Japanese)



**PROJECTS** 

<u>Tic Tac Toe</u> <u>Show us your Quack</u> <u>Safehaven</u>

# Hugh Sinclair

# **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**



#### SUMMARY

I'm a former tech retail sales expert, freshly having completed a Software Engineering immersive in 2022. I love helping others find tech solutions, and this new branch of career will help me create some of those solutions instead of just knowing about them!



## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **General Assembly**

#### **INSTRUCTIONAL ASSISTANT MAR 2022 - AUGUST 2022**

- Creating warmup exercises for various technical levels, ensuring talented students were extended and less experienced students were motivated with achievable tasks
- Assisting students with technical issues, coaching, mentoring and support as they learn to code.
- · Guiding students to find their own solutions.
- Working with head instructor to maintain class flow, while monitoring student needs.
- Creating and maintaining a Gitbook with class notes and revision for students to return to.

#### **General Assembly**

# **SOFTWARE ENGINEER NOV 2021-FEB 2022**

- Completed over 500 hours of progressional training over thirteen

  wooks
- Developed a portfolio showcasing various computer languages such as CSS, HTML, Javascript and Ruby, combined with frameworks such as React and Rails, handling APIs
- Worked within a small team to demonstrate concepts learned over the course of the thirteen weeks.

## Officeworks

# TECH SPECIALIST NOV 2020 - NOV 2021

- Assisted clients with finding technical solutions for local networking, router/modem setup.
- Worked with other tech specialists to quickly resolve any issues that occurred onsite.
- Managed the training of other co-workers in tech areas to address any gaps in knowledge.



### COMMUNITY ENGAGEMENT

JCV (Japan Club Victoria)

## **VOLUNTEER 2015-PRESENT**

Volunteer at multiple events per year, helping run festival events